A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 5 FA1297
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 5
1992-2015
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation
FA1297
30.4 Cubic Feet 80 letter document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Arranged as received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The John A. Hartford Foundation records were donated to RAC by JAHF in 2014. Record transfers to RAC began in 2014 and continue as needed.
Biographical / Historical
The John A. Hartford Foundation (JAHF) was established in 1929 by brothers John and George Hartford, sons of the founder of the Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company (A&P). The foundation is a private, nonpartisan philanthropy dedicated to improving the care of older adults. For its first several decades, the foundation broadly supported clinical medical research. By 1982, it began to focus solely on geriatric healthcare. In 2015, JAHF paid out $20.2 million on a total of 80 active grants and committed $25.3 million to 24 new grants projects, all focused on the care of older adults.
Other Finding Aids
For Series 1 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA771/collection
For Series 2 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1137/collection
For Series 3 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1218/collection
For Series 4 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1296/collection
For Series 6 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1326/collection
For Series 7 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1138/collection
Scope and Contents
The collection contains grant files and associated administrative records from 1992 to 2015 including but not limited to: proposals, award letters, progress reports, correspondence and budget files.
- Grants, 1992-2015; 5
  - Association of American Medical Colleges: M. Brownell Anderson (2005-0121), 2005-2008 (Box 5-1, Folder 1-2)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing: Geraldine Polly Bednash, PhD, RN, AACN (2008-0181) (Box 5-1, Folder 3-4)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing: Geraldine Polly Bednash, PhD, RN, AACN (2005-0023), 2005-2008; Contains digital media (Box 5-1, Folder 5)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing: Geraldine Polly Bednash, PhD, RN, AACN (2005-0023), 2005-2011; Contains digital media (Box 5-2, Folder 6-10)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing: Geraldine Polly Bednash, PhD, RN, AACN (2005-0023), 2001 (Box 5-3, Folder 11)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing: Geraldine Polly Bednash (2004-002), 2004-2014 (Box 5-3, Folder 12-15)
  - American Academy of Nursing: Patricia A. Ford-Roegner, RN, MSW, FAAN (2007-0153), 2007-2012 (Box 5-3, Folder 16)
  - American Academy of Nursing: Patricia A. Ford-Roegner, RN, MSW, FAAN (2007-0153), 2007-2012 (Box 5-4, Folder 17-19)
  - American Academy of Nursing: Patricia G. Archbold, D.N.Sc.: R.N., F.A.A.N. (2005-0202), 2005-2013 (Box 5-4, Folder 20-21)
  - American Academy of Nursing: Patricia G. Archbold, D.N.Sc.: R.N., F.A.A.N. (2005-0202), 2005-2013 (Box 5-5, Folder 22-26)
  - American Academy of Nursing: Patricia G. Archbold, D.N.Sc.: R.N., F.A.A.N. (2005-0202), 2005-2013 (Box 5-6, Folder 27)
  - American Academy of Nursing: Patty D. Franklin, M.S.N., R.N., C.P.N.P. (2003-0023), 2003-2007 (Box 5-6, Folder 28-30)
  - American Academy of Nursing: Patty D. Franklin, M.S.N., R.N., C.P.N.P. (2003-0023), 2003-2007 (Box 5-7, Folder 31)
  - AARP Foundation: Susan C. Reinhard, RN PhD, FAAN (2007-0131), 2007-2009 (Box 5-7, Folder 32-33)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1995-1999 (Box 5-7, Folder 34-35)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1997-2003 (Box 5-8, Folder 36-39)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1996-2004 (Box 5-9, Folder 40-44)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1994-2000 (Box 5-10, Folder 45-48)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1994-2012 (Box 5-11, Folder 49-53)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1994-1998 (Box 5-12, Folder 54-58)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1996-2000 (Box 5-13, Folder 59-62)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc. (94132), 1994-2006 (Box 5-14, Folder 63)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: O. van der Willik (2001-0062), 2001-2005 (Box 5-14, Folder 64-67)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: O. van der Willik (2001-0062), 2001-2005 (Box 5-15, Folder 68)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: S. Lederman (2002-0257), 2002-2005 (Box 5-15, Folder 69)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: O. van der Willik (2004-0332), 2004-2004 (Box 5-15, Folder 70-72)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: O. van der Willik (2004-0332), 2004-2007 (Box 5-16, Folder 73-74)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: Odette van der Willik (2005-0095), 2005-2009 (Box 5-16, Folder 75-77)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: Odette van der Willik (2007-0016), 2007-2012 (Box 5-16, Folder 78)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: Odette van der Willik (2007-0016), 2007-2012 (Box 5-17, Folder 79)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: Odette van der Willik (2003-0086), 2006-2011 (Box 5-17, Folder 80)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: Stephanie Lederman (2003-0086), 2003-2009 (Box 5-17, Folder 81-83)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Inc.: Stephanie Lederman (2003-0086), 2003-2012 (Box 5-18, Folder 84-87)
  - Alliance for Aging Research, 1995-2000 (Box 5-18, Folder 88)
  - Alliance for Aging Research, 1995-2000 (Box 5-19, Folder 89-91)
  - Alliance for Aging Research, 1995-2000 (Box 5-20, Folder 92)
  - The Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Program - Publications, 1995-1996 (Box 5-20, Folder 93-94)
  - The Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Program - Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 5-21, Folder 95)
  - American Geriatrics Society, Inc.: Kevin P. High, M.D., M.Sc. (2004-0153), 2004-2008 (Box 5-21, Folder 96-97)
  - American Geriatrics Society, Inc.: Nancy E. Lundebjerg, MPA (2006-0411), 2006-2013 (Box 5-21, Folder 98-99)
  - American Geriatrics Society, Inc.: Nancy E. Lundebjerg, MPA (2006-0411), 2006-2013 (Box 5-22, Folder 100-103)
  - American Geriatrics Society, Inc.: John R. Burton, M.D. (2004-0208), 2004-2011 (Box 5-22, Folder 104)
  - American Geriatrics Society, Inc.: John R. Burton, M.D. (2004-0208), 2004-2012 (Box 5-23, Folder 105-109)
  - American Geriatrics Society (Box 5-24, Folder 110-113)
  - American Geriatrics Society (Box 5-25, Folder 114)
  - American Board of Internal Medicine (Box 5-25, Folder 115)
  - American Geriatrics Society (94269) (Box 5-25, Folder 116-117)
  - American Geriatrics Society (94269) (Box 5-26, Folder 118-119)
  - American Geriatrics Society: William R. Hazzard (990247), Contains Digital material. (Box 5-26, Folder 120-121)
  - American Geriatrics Society: William R. Hazzard (990247), Contains Digital material. (Box 5-27, Folder 122-125)
  - American Geriatrics Society: William R. Hazzard (990247) (Box 5-28, Folder 126-131)
  - American Geriatrics Society: William R. Hazzard (990247) (Box 5-29, Folder 132-133)
  - American Federation for Aging Research: Stephanie Lederman (2007-0229), 2007-2013 (Box 5-29, Folder 134-136)
  - Kensington Foundation, 2006-2009 (Box 5-29, Folder 137)
  - Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program - Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 5-30, Folder 138-139)
  - Association of Professors of Medicine: Kevin P. High, M.D. (2006-0239) (Box 5-30, Folder 140-142)
  - Association of Professors of Medicine: Kevin P. High, M.D. (2006-0239) (Box 5-31, Folder 143-146)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs.: David B. Reuben, M.D. (2004-0076), 2004-2007 (Box 5-31, Folder 147)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs: Gregg A. Warshaw, M.D. (2005-0257), 2005-2009 (Box 5-32, Folder 148-151)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs: Sharon A. Levine, MD (2007-0126), 2007-2013 (Box 5-32, Folder 152)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs: Sharon A. Levine, MD (2007-0126), 2007-2013 (Box 5-33, Folder 153-155)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology, ASCO Foundation: Hyman B. Muss, M.D. (2005-0195), 2005-2009 (Box 5-33, Folder 156-157)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO), 2000-2003 (Box 5-34, Folder 158-161)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO): Charles M. Balch, M.D. (2002-0023), 2000-2004 (Box 5-34, Folder 162)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO): Charles M. Balch, M.D. (2002-0023) (Box 5-35, Folder 163)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO): Charles M. Balch, M.D. (2000-0418) (Box 5-35, Folder 164-166)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO): Charles M. Balch, M.D. (2000-0418) (Box 5-36, Folder 167-171)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO): Charles M. Balch, M.D. (2000-0418) (Box 5-37, Folder 172-177)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO): Charles M. Balch, M.D. (2000-0418) (Box 5-38, Folder 178)
  - Arizona State University (ASU): Colleen Keller, PhD (2007-0057), 2007-2012 (Box 5-38, Folder 179-183)
  - Council on Social Work Education (CSWE): Nancy Hooyman (2004-0155), 2004-2008 (Box 5-39, Folder 184-185)
  - Council on Social Work Education (CSWE): Julia M. Watkins, Ph.D. (2004-0155), 2004-2008 (Box 5-39, Folder 186-187)
  - Council on Social Work Education (CSWE): Julia M. Watkins, Ph.D. (2004-0155), 2004-2008 (Box 5-40, Folder 188-192)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Julia M. Watkins, Ph.D. (2006-0241), 2006-2009 (Box 5-41, Folder 193-197)
  - Cornell University: M. Carrington Reid, MD, PhD (2008-0141), 2008-2010 (Box 5-41, Folder 198)
  - Cornell University: M. Carrington Reid, MD, PhD (2004-0239), 2004-2009 (Box 5-42, Folder 199)
  - Community College of Philadelphia: M. Elaine Tagliareni, EdD, RN (2008-0274), 2008-2012 (Box 5-42, Folder 200)
  - NLN Foundation for Nursing Education: Mary Anne Rizzolo, EdD, RN (2008-0291), 2008-2012 (Box 5-42, Folder 201)
  - Community College of Philadelphia and NLN Foundation for Nursing Education: M. Elaine Tagliareni, EdD. RN and Mary Anne Rizzolo, EdD, RN (2008-0274 and 2008-0291) (Box 5-42, Folder 202-203)
  - The HOPE Program Advisory Board Meeting, 1992 (Box 5-43, Folder 204)
  - Columbia University - School of Nursing - Caring for Older Adults, 1993-1994 (Box 5-43, Folder 205)
  - Boston Medical Center: Rebecca A. Silliman, M.D., Ph.D. (2003-0202), 2003-2007 (Box 5-43, Folder 206)
  - Boston Medical Center: Rebecca A. Silliman, M.D., Ph.D. (2006-0167), 2006-2010 (Box 5-43, Folder 207)
  - Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center: Lewis A. Lipsitz, M.D. (2006-0077), 2005-2010 (Box 5-43, Folder 208)
  - Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center: Lewis A. Lipsitz, M.D. (2006-0077), 2005-2010 (Box 5-44, Folder 209)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: George E. Taffet, M.D. (2003-0205), 2003-2007 (Box 5-44, Folder 210)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: George E. Taffet, M.D. (2006-0166), 2006-2011 (Box 5-44, Folder 211)
  - Association of Professors of Medicine: Kevin P. High, MD (2006-0239), 2009-2012 (Box 5-44, Folder 212-214)
  - Association of Professors of Medicine: Kevin P. High, MD (2006-0239), 2008-2009 (Box 5-45, Folder 215)
  - Gerontological Society of America: Barbara J. Berkman, D.S.W. (2006-0074), 2006-2012 (Box 5-45, Folder 216-218)
  - Gerontological Society of America: J. Taylor Harden, PhD, RN (2012-0097), 2012-2015 (Box 5-45, Folder 219)
  - Gerontological Society of America: J. Taylor Harden, PhD, RN (2012-0097), 2012-2015 (Box 5-46, Folder 220)
  - George Washington University: Judith Miller Jones (2001-0117), 2000-2005 (Box 5-46, Folder 221-223)
  - George Washington University: Judith Miller Jones (2001-0117), 2000-2005 (Box 5-47, Folder 224-226)
  - George Washington University: Judith Miller Jones (2005-0011) (Box 5-47, Folder 227-228)
  - George Washington University: Judith Miller Jones (2005-0011) (Box 5-48, Folder 229-232)
  - George Washington University: Judith Miller Jones (2008-0007), 2008-2012 (Box 5-48, Folder 233-234)
  - George Washington University: Judith Miller Jones (2008-0007), 2008-2012 (Box 5-49, Folder 235-237)
  - Foundation for L.S.U. Health Sciences Center: Charles A. Cefalu, M.D., M.S. (2006-0207), 2006-2011 (Box 5-49, Folder 238-240)
  - Foundation for Health in Aging, Inc.: Eric A. Coleman, M.D., M.P.H., A.G.S.F (2004-0209), 2004-2010 (Box 5-49, Folder 241)
  - Foundation for Health in Aging, Inc.: Eric A. Coleman, M.D., M.P.H., A.G.S.F (2004-0209), 2004-2010 (Box 5-50, Folder 242-244)
  - Duke University: Kenneth Schmader, MD (2006-0109), 2006-2010 (Box 5-50, Folder 245)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Harvey Jay Cohen, M.D. (2002-0269), 2002-2005 (Box 5-50, Folder 246)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Nancy Hooyman (2001-0136) (Box 5-50, Folder 247)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Nancy Hooyman (2001-0136) (Box 5-51, Folder 248-251)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Nancy Hooyman (2001-0136) (Box 5-52, Folder 252-257)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Nancy Hooyman (2001-0136), Contains Digital Material (Box 5-53, Folder 258-261)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Samuel C. Durso, MD, MBA (2007-0005), 2007-2011 (Box 5-53, Folder 262-263)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Samuel C. Durso, M.D. (2005-0055), 2005-2011 (Box 5-53, Folder 264)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Samuel C. Durso, M.D. (2005-0055), 2005-2011 (Box 5-54, Folder 265)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Charles E. Boult, M.D., M.P.H., M.B.A (2004-0335), 2004-2010 (Box 5-54, Folder 266-270)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Charles E. Boult, M.D., M.P.H., M.B.A (2004-0335), 2004-2010 (Box 5-55, Folder 271)
  - Johns Hopkins University: John R. Burton, M.D. (2002-0264), 2002-2008 (Box 5-55, Folder 272-275)
  - Johns Hopkins University: John Burton (990519), 1999-2006 (Box 5-55, Folder 276)
  - Johns Hopkins University: John Burton (990519), 1999-2006 (Box 5-56, Folder 277-280)
  - International Honor Society of Nursing Foundation, Inc.: Mary Rita Hurley, RN, MPA (2006-0409), 2006-2009 (Box 5-56, Folder 281-282)
  - International Honor Society of Nursing Foundation, Inc.: Mary Rita Hurley, RN, MPA (2006-0409), 2006-2009 (Box 5-57, Folder 283)
  - Intermountain Health Care: Paul D. Clayton (2001-0465), 2002-2004 (Box 5-57, Folder 284-286)
  - Internmountain Health Care Cherie Brunker (2001-0465), 2003-2005 (Box 5-57, Folder 287)
  - Intermountain Health Care: Paul D. Clayton (2001-0465), 2001-2007 (Box 5-58, Folder 288-292)
  - Intermountain Health Care: Paul D. Clayton (2001-0465), 2001-2007 (Box 5-59, Folder 293)
  - Internmountain Health Care Cherie Brunker (2001-0465), 2005-2006 (Box 5-59, Folder 294)
  - Indiana University: Steven R. Counsell, MD (2008-0144), 2008-2010 (Box 5-59, Folder 295)
  - Indiana University: Steven R. Counsell, MD (2004-0323), 2004-2009 (Box 5-59, Folder 296)
  - Harvard Medical School: Lewis A. Lipsitz, M.D. (2002-0267), 2002-2005 (Box 5-59, Folder 297)
  - Grantmakers in Aging: John Feather (2011-0176), 2011-2014 (Box 5-59, Folder 298)
  - Gerontological Society of America: Barbara J. Berkman, D.S.W. (2006-0074), 2006-2012 (Box 5-60, Folder 299-302)
  - National PACE Association: Peter Fitzgerald (2001-0163), 2003 (Box 5-60, Folder 303)
  - National PACE Association: Peter Fitzgerald (2001-0163), 2003 (Box 5-61, Folder 304)
  - National PACE Association: Shawn Bloom (2000-0290), 1999-2001 (Box 5-61, Folder 305-306)
  - National PACE Association: Shawn M. Bloom (2001-0163) (Box 5-61, Folder 307)
  - National PACE Association: Shawn M. Bloom (2001-0163) (Box 5-62, Folder 308-312)
  - National Council on the Aging: Nancy A. Whitelaw (2001-0123), 2002-2004 (Box 5-62, Folder 313)
  - National Council on the Aging: Nancy A. Whitelaw (2001-0123), 2001-2005 (Box 5-63, Folder 314-318)
  - National Council on the Aging: Nancy A. Whitelaw (2001-0123), 2001-2002 (Box 5-64, Folder 319)
  - National Council on Aging: Whitehall (2004-0080) (Box 5-64, Folder 320)
  - Mount Sinai Medial Center, Inc.: Rosanne M. Leipzig, M.D., Ph.D. (2006-0098), 2006-2010 (Box 5-64, Folder 321)
  - Mount Sinai Medial Center, Inc.: Rosanne M. Leipzig, M.D., Ph.D. (2005-0058), 2005-2009 (Box 5-64, Folder 322)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine: Rosanne M. Leipzig, M.D., PhD. (2002-0272), 2002-2006 (Box 5-64, Folder 323)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center, Inc.: Diane E. Meier, M.D. (2005-0171), 2009 (Box 5-64, Folder 324)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center, Inc.: Diane E. Meier, M.D. (2005-0171), 2006-2009 (Box 5-65, Folder 325-330)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center, Inc.: Diane E. Meier, M.D. (2009-0137), 2009-2013 (Box 5-66, Folder 331-332)
  - Meridian Institute: Timothy J. Mealey (2008-0006), 2007-2011 (Box 5-66, Folder 333)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Bruce Leff, M.D. (2004-0333), 2004-2011 (Box 5-66, Folder 334-336)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Bruce Leff, M.D. (2004-0333), 1999; 2004-2011 (Box 5-67, Folder 337-339)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Charles E. Boult, MD, MPH, MBA (2007-0322) (Box 5-67, Folder 340)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2000-0546), 2002-2003 (Box 5-67, Folder 341-342)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2000-0546), 2000-2003; Contains digital material (Box 5-68, Folder 343-346)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2000-0546), 2003-2004; Contains digital material (Box 5-69, Folder 347-349)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2000-0546), 2004-2005; Contains digital material (Box 5-70, Folder 350-353)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2000-0546), 2005 (Box 5-71, Folder 354-357)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2000-0546), 2005-2006; Contains digital material (Box 5-72, Folder 358-561)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2000-0546), 2001-2007 (Box 5-73, Folder 562-566)
  - New York University: Mathy Mezey (2004-0152), 2004-2009 (Box 5-73, Folder 567)
  - New York University: John Sexton, J.D., Ph.D. (2004-0401) (Box 5-74, Folder 568)
  - New York University: Mathy D. Mezey, Ed..D.. R.N.. F.A.A.N. (2004-0280) (Box 5-74, Folder 569)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: Patricia J. Volland (2005-0014), 2005-2009 (Box 5-74, Folder 570-575)
  - National PACE Association: Peter Fitzgerald (2007-0017) (Box 5-75, Folder 576-578)
  - RAND Corporation: Harold Alan Pincus, M.D. (2005-0193) (Box 5-75, Folder 579-580)
  - RAND Corporation: Harold Alan Pincus, M.D. (2006-0230), 2006-2009 (Box 5-76, Folder 581-582)
  - Project Hope - People to People Health Foundation, Inc.: John K. Inglehart (2005-0019), 2004-2007 (Box 5-76, Folder 583)
  - Preventative Medicine Research Institute: Dean Ornish, MD (2007-0011), 2007-2008 (Box 5-76, Folder 584)
  - Pennsylvania State University: Ann Kolanowski, PhD, RN (2007-0059), 2007-2014 (Box 5-76, Folder 585-586)
  - Pennsylvania State University: Ann Kolanowski, PhD, RN (2007-0059), 2007-2014 (Box 5-77, Folder 587-589)
  - Peace Health Oregon Region: Ron Stock (2000-0381) (Box 5-77, Folder 590-591)
  - Peace Health Oregon Region: Ron Stock (2000-0381) (Box 5-78, Folder 592-596)
  - Peace Health Oregon Region: Ron M. Stock, M.D. (2004-0228), 2004-2005 (Box 5-78, Folder 597)
  - Partners in Care Foundation, Inc.: W. June Simmons, L.C.S.W. (2006-0127), 2006-2011 (Box 5-79, Folder 598-599)
  - Paraprofessional Healthcare Institute, Inc.: Steven L. Dawson (2010-0186), 2010-2012 (Box 5-79, Folder 600-601)
  - Paraprofessional Healthcare Institute: Sara Joffe (2006-0080), 2006-2011 (Box 5-79, Folder 602)
  - Paraprofessional Healthcare Institute: Sara Joffe (2006-0080), 2006-2011 (Box 5-80, Folder 603-606)
  - Oregon Health Science University: Patricia Archbold Progress Report Overflow (2000-0097), 2001-2003 (Box 5-80, Folder 607-608)